njoyn.com 2015-10-21

# Njoyn: Privacy Policy

CGI Group Inc. (“CGI”) respects the privacy of its Web site visitors and is committed to protecting the privacy rights of identifiable individuals. In this regard, CGI has prepared this Web Site Privacy Policy (the “Privacy Policy”) to communicate to its users how CGI collects, uses and discloses personal information collected about them on the CGI Web site. This Privacy Policy applies to www.cgi.com and its authorized sub-sites that expressly adopt, display or link back to this Privacy Policy.

**Collection and Use of Personal Information**  
We may collect personal information such as your name, personal home address, personal e-mail address and personal telephone and fax numbers that you voluntarily provide to us when you request information about our services, submit questions, register for services, or when you submit your resume in relation to a career opportunity. The aforementioned personal information provided by you may then be used to communicate with you in connection with your various inquiries or to consider you for employment purposes.

We may also collect information in connection with your visit to our Web site through the use of cookies. Such information will be used to analyze trends, to administer the site, to track visitors’ movements around the site and to gather demographic information about our visitor base as a whole. The use of cookies merely identifies you as a number, that is, your name, address or any other information that directly identifies you will not be collected. Additional details regarding the use of various technologies are provided below.

**Disclosure of Personal Information**  
We may disclose the personal information collected through this Web site with our affiliates for internal business purposes.

We may also share information provided by you with service providers that we retain to perform services on our behalf. These service providers are contractually limited from using or disclosing the information except as is necessary to perform the services or to comply with legal requirements. Furthermore, we may disclose information about you where we are required or permitted by law to do so.

**Links to non-CGI websites**  
This Web site may contain links to third party Web sites that are not affiliated with CGI. CGI does not in any way endorse or make any representations about such third party Web sites. The links are simply made available for your convenience. As such, CGI is not responsible for the privacy practices or content of such third party Web sites. If you choose to access those links, we encourage you to review their respective privacy policies before submitting any of your personal information.

**Our Security Measures to Protect Personal Information**  
To protect the personally identifiable information you transmit through your use of this Web site, we maintain reasonable physical, technical and administrative safeguards to help protect against the unauthorized access, use and disclosure of the information.

**Access and Correction**  
Using our Contact Us page, you may request information about the existence of the personal information voluntarily provided by you through our Website, and request access to such information in order to have it deleted, updated or corrected, subject to certain legal restrictions.

**Use of Technology: Cookies & Logs**  
As previously mentioned, CGI may use cookies to collect information about its visitors. Cookies are identifiers that are transferred to your computer’s hard drive through your Web browser to enable our systems to recognize your browser. You may choose to disable cookies on your computer by modifying your Web browser.

CGI may also use logs to collect information about its visitors. CGI may review server logs for security purposes, for example, to detect intrusions into our network. Server log data, which contains visitors’ IP addresses, could in instances of criminal malfeasance be used to trace and identify individuals. In such instances, raw data logs would be shared with appropriate investigative bodies authorized to investigate such breaches of security. Like cookies, logs do not cross reference the information automatically collected with any type of personal information that is voluntarily offered by you on or through this Web site.

**Young Audiences**  
This Web site is not intentionally designed for or directed to children and we do not knowingly collect or maintain personal information from children on our Web site. If we become aware that we have inadvertently received personal information from such a visitor, we will delete the information from our records.

**Consent**  
By using this Web site and sub-sites, you consent to the collection, use and disclosure of your personal information by us in the manner described in this Privacy Policy. CGI reserves the right to make changes to this Privacy Policy from time to time without notice.

**Privacy Questions and Access**  
For additional information about our online privacy practices, please contact:

The Privacy Officer  
CGI Group Inc.  
1350 René-Lévesque Boulevard West  
15th floor  
Montreal, Quebec H3G 1T4  
Canada
